# **Febrianus Arif** Munandar Laia

082289522036

febrianusarif19@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/febrianusarifmlaia



Lubuk Begalung, Padang

## **Profile Summary**

I am a fresh graduate of Information Systems with a focus on Front End Development. Skilled in HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, and Bootstrap, and experienced in developing Decision Support System (DSS) based website during my PKL at Padang City Fisheries and Food Agency. Committed to continuous learning and adapting quickly, I am ready to make a positive contribution and get involved in challenging projects in the world of web development.

### **Education**

Universitas Putra Indonesia YPTK Padang | 2020 - 2024

Bachelor of Information Systems - GPA 3.47

## **Work Experience**

Fieldwork Practice | Dinas Perikanan dan Pangan Kota Padang | Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

- Designing a web-based decision support system using the MOORA method.
- This system helps determine which fishermen groups are eligible to receive fish farming assistance.
- Involved needs analysis, development, and implementation of an effective system.

Web Development Project | Dinas Pertanian Kota Padang | Mey 2024 - Jul 2024

- Design and develop a responsive web-based decision support system.
- Using the VIKOR method to select farmer groups that are eligible to receive agricultural production facilities assistance.
- Focus on an interface that is attractive, interactive, and provides useful solutions for government agencies.

#### **Technical Skills**

- · HTML, CSS, dan JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- · PHP
- · MySQL
- · Figma dan Canva

- Project Management
- · Time management
- Effective communication
- Adaptable

- Interpersonal skills
- · Problem solving
- · Focus and Discipline
- Creative and Innovative